marketersoftware.com 2019-10-10

# The Expert Digital Marketing Privacy Policy | Morrison Publishing

This Privacy Policy applies to your use of http://www.MorrisonPublishing.com, http://www.MorrisonEducation.com, http://anthonymorrison.clickfunnels.com, http://www.anthonymorrison.com or any other URL (the “Site” or “Website(s)”) owned by Morrison Publishing, LLC its subsidiaries, affiliates and partners (collectively the “Company.”) Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience on the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use the Internet's vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence.

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how our company collects information from all end users of our products and services (collectively the "Services") - those who access some of our Services but do not have accounts ("Visitors") as well as those who may purchase Products and/or pay a monthly service fee to subscribe to the Service ("Members") - what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Members have concerning the collection and use of such information. We request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

By visiting our Site, you are consenting to our policy of collecting and using your data.

**Personal Information Our Company Collects and How It Is Used**

**Introduction:**

Our company collects information in different ways from Visitors and Members who access the various parts of our Services and the network of Websites accessible through our Service. We do not specifically target customers in the EU, however, we have updated our Privacy Policy and will continue to remain compliant and up to date on all policies and requirements. Our commitment is to your privacy and protection of your data.

**Registration:**

Members may be asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Products or Services including name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access the Services. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Member's account (such as for billing purposes). This information may be shared with third parties, as stated herein, or in special circumstances.

However, in instances where our company and a partner jointly promote our Services, we may provide the partner certain personal information, such as the name, address, phone number of persons who subscribed to the Services as a result of the joint promotion for the purpose of offering you other products and services.

We may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information Members provide during registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of Members). As explained in more detail below, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to sell advertisements that appear on the Services.

Our Company collects personal information through forms you complete on the site, as well as but not limited to contests, sweepstakes, text messages, Facebook messages, e-mails, faxes, telephone calls, postal mail or other communications with the user, as well as from outside sources such as credit card processors and database vendors. For example, when you fill out a form subscribing to our emails, we are sent data information from our autoresponder company such as your name, email, the website you signed up from, geographical data such as your city, state, Postal code, country, Latitude, Longitude, Timestamp, Subscription method and IP address. Also, with purchases, we supply our member's contact information, to our business partners, who then may contact the member by telephone after the member purchase. Sales proceeds are collected by the business partner company. We also may supply other companies with contact information, for mail or email offers we believe would be of interest to our members, with or without compensation from those companies. At times we may send an advertisement for a third-party product, where we collect the sales proceeds, and forward the purchaser's information to that third party.

**Our Company Partners and Sponsors:**

Some products and services may be offered to Visitors and Members in conjunction with an affiliate, independent contractor seller or non-affiliated partner. To provide Visitors and Members some of these products and services, the partner may need to collect and maintain personal information.

**Online Shopping:**

You can purchase products and services or register to receive materials, such as a newsletter, catalog or new product and service updates from our Site. In many cases, you may be asked to provide contact information, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and credit/debit card information. If you complete an order for someone else, such as an online gift order sent directly to a recipient, you may be asked to provide information about the recipient, such as the recipient's name, address, and phone number. Our Company has no control over the third parties' use of any personal information you provide when placing such an order. Please exercise care when doing so. If you order services or products directly from our company, we use the personal information you provide to process that order. We do share this information with outside parties that we do business with.

**Online Advertisements:**

Our Company may display online advertisements. In those cases we share information about our Visitors and Members collected through the registration process as well as through online surveys and promotions with these advertisers. Additionally, in some instances, we use this information to deliver tailored advertisements or joint ventures. For instance, an advertiser or joint venture company tells us the audience they want to reach and provides us an advertisement tailored to the audience. Based upon the information we have collected, we may then display or send the advertisement to the intended audience. Our company does share personal information about its Visitors or Members with these advertisers or joint venture companies.

By visiting our Company Website, you are consenting to our policy of collecting and using your data. If you do not want to consent to our policy of collecting and using your data you can “opt out” of our Re-Targeting, Social Network and Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads advertising policy by notifying Company in the following manner:

**Re-Targeting & Behavioral Targeting**

Our company partners with a 3rd party ad network to display our advertising on other websites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this website as well as others. This information is used to provide you targeted advertising across the Internet, based on your interests. Our Company may utilize categories of information, including names and email addresses, collected from users on our sites and services, as well as third party sites and services, in connection with the ads that are served. This advertising may include, but not limited to, contextual advertising, cookies, anonymous cookies, pixels, persistent identifiers, geo-location information, email opt in, search engine terms, behavioral advertising and/or retargeting advertising. This type of advertising is a form of targeted advertising, to the specific individual who is visiting the Web site. These advertisements appear on websites or other media, including display ads, pop up ads and ads displayed in mobile browsers.

Our Company does not conduct inquiries into the information collection practices of third parties that may collect information from users that leave our Web site. Our Company may share customer information with third parties to process orders, for third party analytics and for marketing and advertising purposes.

If you would like to have this information not used for the purpose of showing you targeted ads, you may opt-out by going to this website (http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). If you are located in the European Union you may change your preferences by going to this website (http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). This does not opt you out of being served advertising it only ensures your information will not be used by us to serve targeted ads. You will still receive generic advertising across the Internet, which has nothing to do with our company.

**Social Network and Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads (WCA):**

A Custom Audience on Facebook.com is a list of people our company would like to show our ads to on Facebook.com, who have shown interest in our products and services, with ads we believe would be of interest to them. This audience consists of people, whose information and email addresses our Company already has, because they have already subscribed to receiving Company emails. If you no longer have an interest in our products and services, you can opt-out of seeing Company's Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads. Unsubscribing from our Company's email list will remove you from Company's internal email database list and stop future emails from our Company, but not from being shown Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads. The Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads external database, is different from our Company's internal database and requires the following Opting-out request.

Opting-out of Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads: To opt out of our Company's Facebook.com Custom Audience Ads, send an email, from the email address you are opting out, to Company using our email address provided in Company's contact information. Put "Opting Out of Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads" in the subject line of the email. In the body of the email include your name and email address. Our Company staff will forward your name and email address to Facebook.com with a request to delete you from all of Company's Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads.

**Google.com Analytics:**

Our Company may use Analytics tracking code to support Display Advertising, and enable Google Analytics to collect data about your traffic via the DoubleClick cookie in addition to data collected through the standard Google Analytics implementation. Display Advertising lets us enable features in Analytics that aren't available through standard implementations, like Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.

Our Company may use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online: This allows third-party vendors, including Google, to show your ads on sites across the Internet. Our Company and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to our website.

Our Company may implement Google Display Network Impression Reporting or the DoubleClick Campaign Manager: Our Company and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services that are related to visits to your site.

Our Company may implement Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting: The data from Google's Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) with Google Analytics allows us to serve ads to you based on this data.

Opting-out of Google Analytics' For The Web and Google Analytics for Display Advertising: Users can opt-out of Google Analytics' currently available opt-outs for the web at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/

Using the Ads Settings, users can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads at https://www.google.com/settings/personalinfo

**Responses to Email Inquiries:**

When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to our company, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive.

**Voluntary Customer Surveys:**

We may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. We encourage our customers to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of products and services we offer and how we provide them to you.

We may take the information we receive from individuals responding to our Customer Surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other customers we may have, to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). We then use the aggregated information to improve the quality of our services to you, and to develop new services and products. This aggregated; non-personally identifying information may be shared with third parties.

**Special Cases:**

It is our company's policy to use or share the personal information about Visitors or Members in ways described herein without additional notice or means to opt-out except as noted herein, or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. Also, we may disclose personal information about Visitors or Members, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: credit agencies, collection agencies, merchant database agencies, law enforcement, or to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, the Child Online Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or Terms Of Service, or other user policies; to operate the Services properly; or to protect our company and our Members.

**Legal Bases for Processing (for EEA users):**

If you are an individual in the European Economic Area (EEA), we collect and process information about you only where we have legal bases for doing so under applicable EU laws. The legal bases depend on the Services you use and how you use them. This means we collect and use your information only where:

o We need it to provide you the Services, including to operate the Services, provide customer support and personalized features and to protect the safety and security of the Services;

o It satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your data protection interests), such as for research and development, to market and promote the Services and to protect our legal rights and interests;

o You give us consent to do so for a specific purpose; or

o We need to process your data to comply with a legal obligation.

If you have consented to our use of information about you for a specific purpose, you have the right to change your mind at any time, but this will not affect any processing that has already taken place. Where we are using your information because we or a third party have a legitimate interest to do so, you have the right to object to that use though, in some cases, this may mean no longer using the Services.

**An Understanding Of How We Use Your Information**

Information we collect may be used in the following ways:

\- To notify you of updates to our Site or any Products and Services we offer.  
\- To respond to your request or inquires.  
\- To share offers from other companies with you.  
\- To conduct market research and analysis.  
\- To validate your identity.  
\- To keep records of our interactions with you if you place an order or deal with a customer support representative.  
\- To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights.  
\- To provide you with newsletters, articles or products, Products or Services.  
\- To provide you with alerts and announcements.  
\- To process and complete your transactions for orders, customer service, billing and otherwise to fulfill our contractual obligation to you as a customer.  
\- To analyze purchase history and transactions to improve our products, services and programs.  
\- To prevent, investigate or provide notice of fraud, unlawful or criminal activity, or unauthorized access to or us of personally identifiable information.  
\- To fulfill any other purpose for which you provided your personally identifiable information us.

**Email Marketing**

With respect to personal data that we do not maintain or control, you may also may also make your request to access, view, update, delete or port your personal data (where available), or to update your subscription preferences, by following the links at the bottom of any email communication you receive by clicking the “unsubscribe” link or the “manage subscription” link.

For other requests, contacting us at privacy@morrisonpublishing.com with the subject line “Opt Out Of Email Marketing” and we will take care of that request immediately.

These are the email marketing platforms you may be subscribed to:

• AWEBER  
• Ontraport  
• Active Campaign  
• SendLane  
• Get Response

If you make a request to delete your personal data and that data is necessary for the products or services you have purchased, the request will be honored only to the extent it is no longer necessary for any Services purchased or required for our legitimate business purposes or legal or contractual record keeping requirements. If you make a request to obtain a copy of or port your personal data, to the extent we have any, we will respond within a reasonable time frame.

We utilize 5 different email-marketing platforms due to the fact that each one has features and functionality that the other does not. We use each platform for a specific type of correspondence with you; however, you are able to opt-out at the bottom of any and all emails that we send to you. If you’d like us to remove you from every platform at once you can send that request to privacy@morrisonpublishing.com with the subject line “Opt Out Of Email Marketing” and we will take care of that request immediately.

To our knowledge all of our data controllers have sent out updates that they are now GDRP compliant. We will continue to monitor and make sure that we only utilize companies who are in compliance with all regulatory requirements.

**Your Rights**

You have the right to request any personally identifiable information we have on file about you. If you would like a copy of this information you can contact us at privacy@morrisonpublishing.com to request it. We will require proof of your identity before sharing this information. If you find that our information is out of date you may ask us to update that information.

In the event that your information is within one of our 3rd party Email Marketing programs listed above you can always change or update that information as well as your settings by following the links at the bottom of any emails sent to you by our company.

You may ask us to delete all of your information. It may not be possible for us to delete all of the information we hold about you where we are fulfilling a transaction or have a legal basis to retain the information, however, feel free to contact us and we can assist you with your request.

If you are receiving emails from us and no longer wish to have them to sent to you all you need to do is click the ‘manage subscription’ or ‘unsubscribe’ buttons at the bottom of any and all emails. This does not apply to transactional based emails where are required to send you proof of purchase and fulfillment of our contractual obligations to deliver purchased products to you.

**"Cookies" and How Our Company Uses Them.**

A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. Our company may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for purposes stated herein as well as for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks.

**Your Consent:**

By continuing to use and navigate our Sites and use our Services you are agreeing to our use of cookies, web beacons and similar technologies as described herein.

Cookies are essentially small data files placed on your computer, tablet, mobile phone or other device (“collectively, a “device”) that allows us to record information when you visit or interact with our websites, service, applications, messaging, and other tools. Though often these technologies are generically referred to as “Cookies,” each functions slightly differently, and is better explained below:

**Cookies:** These are small text files (typically made up of letters and numbers) placed in the memory of your browser or device when you visit a website or view a message. Cookies allow a website to recognize a particular device or browser. There are several types of cookies:

• Session cookies expire at the end of your browser session and allow us to link your actions during that particular browser session.

• Persistent cookies are stored on your device in between browser sessions, allowing us to remember your preferences or actions across multiple sites.

• First-party cookies are those set by a website that is being visited by the user at the time in order to preserve your settings (e.g., while on our site).

• Third-party cookies are placed in your browser by a website, or domain, that is not the website or domain that you are currently visiting. If a user visits a website and another entity sets a cookie through that website this would be a third-party cookie.

When you enter a website using cookies, you may be asked to fill out a form providing personal information; like your name, e-mail address, and interests. This information is packaged into a cookie and sent to your browser (Chrome, Firefox, etc.), which then stores the information for later use. The next time you go to the same website, your browser will send the cookie to the server. The message is sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.

**Web Beacons:** small files (also called “pixels”, “image tags”, or “script tags”) that may be loaded on our Sites that may work in concert with cookies to identify our users and provide anonymized data on their behavior.

**Similar Technologies:** Technologies that store information in your browser or device utilizing local shared objects or local storage, such as flash cookies, HTML 5 cookies, and other web application software methods. These technologies can operate across all of your browsers, and in some instances may not be fully managed by your browser and may require management directly through your installed applications or device. We do not use these technologies for storing information to target advertising to you on or off our sites.

**What Types of Cookies, Web Beacons and Similar Technologies Do We Use and Why:**

Our cookies, web beacons and similar technologies serve various purposes, but are generally either necessary or essential to the functioning of our sites, services, applications, tools or messaging, help us improve the performance of or provide you extra functionality of the same, or help us to serve relevant and targeted advertisements. More specifically:

**Strictly Necessary or Essential:** 'Strictly necessary' or ‘essential’ cookies, web beacons and similar technologies let you move around Site and use our Services. Without these technologies, Services you have asked for cannot be provided. Please note that these technologies do not gather any information about you that could be used for marketing or remembering where you've been on the internet. Accepting these technologies is a condition of using our sites, services, applications, tools or messaging, so if you prevent these from loading we can't guarantee your use or how the security therein will perform during your visit.

**Performance:** 'Performance' cookies, web beacons and similar technologies collect information about how you use our website e.g. which pages you visit, and if you experience any errors. These cookies do not collect any information that could identify you and is only used to help us improve how Site, understand what interests our users and measure how effective our content is by providing anonymous statistics and data regarding how our website is used. Accepting these technologies is a condition of using our Sites and Services, so if you prevent these from loading we can't guarantee your use or how the security therein will perform during your visit.

**Functionality:** These cookies, web beacons or similar technologies are used to provide Services or to remember settings to improve your visit.

**Advertising:** First or third-party cookies and web beacons may be placed by our Sites or Services in order to deliver content, including product related advertisements, relevant to your specific interests on our sites or third-party sites. These technologies allow us to understand how useful our advertisements are, and improve the relevancy of the content delivered to our users.

We also utilize 3rd party service providers to assist us in delivering on the same functions, which means that our authorized service providers may also place cookies, web beacons and similar technologies on your device via our services (third party cookies). They may also collect information that helps them identify your device, such as IP-address, or other unique or device identifiers.

**How To Manage, Control and Delete Cookies, Web Beacons and Similar Technologies:**

You may block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our Sites or Services. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon as you visit our Site.

Internet browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. These settings are usually found in the 'options' or 'preferences' menu of your internet browser. In order to understand these settings, the following links may be helpful. Otherwise you should use the 'Help' option in your internet browser for more details.

• [Cookie settings in Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies)  
• [Cookie settings in Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences)  
• [Cookie settings in Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&hl=en)  
• [Cookie settings in Safari](https://support.apple.com/kb/ph19214?locale=en_US)

If you wish to withdraw your consent at any time, you will need to delete your cookies using your internet browser settings.

**More Information About Cookies:**

• Useful information about cookies, including information about deleting or blocking cookies, can be found at: [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

• A guide to behavioral advertising and online privacy has been produced by the internet advertising industry which can be found at: [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)

• Information on the ICC (UK) UK cookie guide can be found on the ICC website section:  
<http://www.international-chamber.co.uk/our-expertise/digitaleconomy>

**Deleting Cookies:**

If you don't want our Company's cookies on your computer, to be used for the purposes stated herein, they are easy to delete. Simply go to <http://wiht.link/cookiesguide> for instructions.

Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

**Public Forums:**

Please remember that any information you may disclose in any Member Directory, or other public areas of our Websites or the Internet, becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas.

**Our Company's Commitment to Data Security:**

Services and Sites we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect any and all personal identifiable information given to us by our customers.

While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.

When you make a purchase from our company any sensitive information is entered on pages using orders forms that have encrypted information using SSL.

**Transfer of Personal Data Abroad:**

If you utilize our Services from a country other than the country where our servers are located, your communications with us may result in transferring your personal data across international borders. Also, when you call us or initiate a chat, we may provide you with support from one of our global locations outside your country of origin. In these cases, your personal data is handled according to this Privacy Policy. You understand that we may transfer information about in in the United States and other countries, which may have different data protection laws than those in the country you reside.

**Notice to California Residents – Your California Privacy Rights:**

Under California Law SB 27, California residents have the right to receive, once a year, information about third parties with whom we have shared information about you or your family for their marketing purposes during the previous calendar year, and a description of the categories of personal information shared. To make such a request, please send an email to Company, to the email address provided in our contact information and please include the phrase "California Privacy Request" in the subject line, the domain name of the Web site you are inquiring about, along with your name, address and email address. We will respond to you within thirty days of receiving such a request.

**IF YOU ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THIS WEB SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THIS WEB SITE, FALLS WITHIN THE CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (COPPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING SO.**

**Where to Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy:**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us through the contact information provided on this Web site.

We comply with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to each Privacy Shield Framework, we are subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

To easily access, view, update, delete or port your personal data (where available), or to update your subscription preferences, please sign into your Account and visit “User Profile.” Please Contact Us [privacy@morrisonpublishing.com](mailto:privacy@morrisonpublishing.com) for additional information and guidance for accessing, updating or deleting data.

**Revisions to This Policy:**

Our company reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our Terms of Service agreement, and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner, by updating this posting. Your use of this site after such changes are implemented constitutes your acknowledgement and acceptance of these changes. Please consult this privacy statement prior to every use for any changes.

Privacy Policy Updated May 24th, 2018
